Guide to the Judy Richardson Papers, 1963-2014 RL.10177
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 9
  - Queen Nzinga (Box 16)
    Short story
  - Race relations (Box 16)
  - Slavery chronology (Box 16)
  - Slavery, general, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Slavery in New England, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Slavery in New York (Box 16)
  - SNCC (Box 16)
  - Southern Africa, 1972 (Box 16)
    Report by the Center for Black Education
  - Till, Emmett (Box 16)
  - Wakayama, Tamio (Box 16)
    Short story: Soul on Rice
  - Washington, Harold (Box 16)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1971-2013; 4 Linear Feet 177 sound and moving image recordings
  The Audiovisual Materials Series contains interviews with and speeches by Judy Richardson, works pertaining to African American history, the Civil Rights Movement and social justice issues, and Richardson's voiceover work.
  - Interviews and programs related to African American history, the Civil Rights Movement, and social justice issues, 1971-2013; 1
    - News Stories Wilmington 10, circa 1971; 1
      - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Umatic-0001)
    - WBUR FM: Interview with Judy Richardson on "The Struggle", 1979 April 19; 2
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0030)
    - People Power: Children's Book Festival, 1980 December 14, 17; 3
      - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Umatic-0002)
    - J Richardson and Joanne Grant RE: Ms Ella Baker, 1986 December 22; 4
      - Original audiocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0039)
    - All Things Considered #880426: SNCC Reunion, 1988; 5
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0014)
    - "Nightwatch" on Mississippi Burning, 1988 January 5; 6
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0057)
    - CBS Nightwatch: Judy Richardson, 1988 January 6; 7
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0036)
    - "Mississippi Burning", 1989 January 6; 9
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0056)
    - World Monitor, 1989 February 7; 8
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0058)
    - Judy Richardson Speech at Martin Luther King Jr's Day at Faith United Church of Christ, 1990 January 15; 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0015)
    - Judy Richardson Speech USF, 1990 February 27; 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0008)
    - WMNF Radio Tampa, 1990 February 28; 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0011)
    - Judy Richardson Interview on WFXT Fox, 1991 January 20; 13
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0060)
    - Martin Luther King Breakfast Part 1, 1991 January 21; 14
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0025)
    - Martin Luther King Breakfast Part 2, 1991 January 21; 15
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0014)
    - Richardson Speech at Niagra University, 1991 March 6; 16
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0035)
    - JR at Teens as Community Resources, 1991 May 2; 17
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0009)
    - Walter Bishop, 1992 October 3; 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0010)
    - Flashback, 1994 June 19; 21
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0022)
    - "Turning Point" ABC-TV Freedom Summer and Judy Richardson on "Chronicle" and Freedom Summer, 1994 August 17 and 1995 August 15; 19
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0005)
    - The Rise of Apartheid and The Fall of Apartheid, 1994; 20
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0020)
    - Flashback: Martin Luther King, 1995 February 4; 22
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0016)
    - Freedom Summer and Urban Update, 1995 May 21 and August 15; 26
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0021)
    - Black Commerce Crusade, 1995 June 10; 25
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0018)
    - Power and Money Panel: Building Social Capital as Part of the Equation for Changing the World Tape 1, 1995; 23
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0012)
    - Power and Money Panel: Building Social Capital as Part of the Equation for Changing the World Tape 2, 1995; 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0013)
    - Civil Rights: Leadership in America, 1997 June 24; 27
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0039)
    - Civil Rights: Leadership in America, 1997 June 24; 28
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0043)
    - Civil Rights: Leadership in America, 1997 June 24; 29
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0055)
    - Civil Rights: Leadership in America, 1997 June 24; 30
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0061)
    - Rock of Changes (Narration by Judy Richardson), 1998; 38
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0026)
    - Rock of Change: Race, Faith, and Freedom, 1998 February 26; 35
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0023)
    - Interview with Gloria Richardson Dandridge Part 1, 1998 February 7; 36
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0005)
    - Interview with Gloria Richardson Dandridge Part 2, 1998 February 7; 37
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0006)
    - Life and Career of Kwame Toure Part 1, 1998 April 15; 31
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0003)
    - Life and Career of Kwame Toure Part 2, 1998 April 15; 32
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0004)
    - Kwame Toure Tribute 1 of 2, 1998 April 8; 33
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0009)
    - Family Name/Africans in America, 1998 August 31; 34
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0050)
    - America's Favorite Poems: Judy Richardson reading Margaret Walker's March on Washington Poem, 1998 November 1; 39
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0021)
    - Africa Today KPFA: Judy Richardson, 1998 November 19; 40
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0019)
    - Democracy Now!: Kwame Toure, 1998 November 23; 41
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0017)
    - Museum of African America History, 1999 August 2; 42
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0046)
    - MAAH final for script check, circa 1999; 43
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0045)
    - Diane Nash Interview, 1999 October 2; 44
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0023)
    - Ezell Blair and Jibreel Khazan Interview, 1999 October 25; 45
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0001)
    - Hopes on the Horizon: Blackside, Inc, 2000 February 16; 53
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0020)
    - City Line and Return to Glory, 2000 February 27; 54
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0024)
    - "Starting Out Safe and Sound", 2000 March; 57
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0027)
    - SNCC Conference #1, 2000 April 13-16; 46
      - Original Mini-DV videocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-MDV-0001)
    - SNCC Conference #2, 2000 April 13-16; 47
      - Original Mini-DV videocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-MDV-0002)
    - SNCC Conference #3, 2000 April 13-16; 48
      - Original Mini-DV videocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-MDV-0003)
    - SNCC Conference, 2000 April 13-16; 49
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0049)
    - Women in Films, 2000 May 16; 58
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0013)
    - Joyce Ladner Speech at SNCC Conference in Raleigh, NC, 2000 April 14; 50
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0007)
    - SNCC Conference, 2000 April 14; 51
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0018)
    - LRTJ Rough Cut, 2000 July 21; 55
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0044)
    - Hopes on the Horizon: Blackside, Inc, 2000 July 28; 56
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0001)
    - Chimes of Freedom "Eyes on the Prize", 2000 December; 52
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0017)
    - Boston Common and Urban Update "The Dilemma of Race", 2001 February 25; 60
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0022)
    - SNCC Women "Urban update", 2001 April 1; 59
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0019)
    - The Challenges of Reform Southwestern High School, 2001; 61
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0051)
    - "Writers on Writing", 2001 May 7; 62
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0054)
    - On the Front Lines: TV and African-American Issues, 2002 February 23; 63
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0053)
    - A Fragile Freedom: African American Historic Sites, 2002 Febraur 13; 64
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0048)
    - A Fragile Freedom: African American Historic Sites, 2002 February; 65
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0047)
    - Urban Update and Fragile Freedom, 2002 February 26; 66
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0041)
    - "A Fragile Freedom," J. RIchardson on "Coming Together", 2002 March 2; 67
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0010)
    - Judy Richardson, Wisconsin Public Radio, 2003 February; 68
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 20, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0001)
    - Remembering SNCC and SDS Panel Discussion, Organization of American Historians Annual Meeting, 2004 April 4; 69
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0019)
    - We Shall Overcome: A living history of the civil rights struggle told in words, pictures, and the voices of the participants, 2004 October 4; 71
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0021)
    - "Will the Circle Be Unbroken: Lessons of the Civil Rights Movement", 2004 November 4; 70
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0062)
    - Mississippi Freedom Movement Radio Documentary by Laura Tilghman, 2005 April 21; 72
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0022)
    - Judy Richardson Interview Part 1, 2005 July 18; 73
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0011)
    - Judy Richardson Interview Part 2, 2005 July 18; 74
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0012)
    - Judy Richardson Interview Part 3, 2005 July 18; 75
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0013)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 1, 2006 March 24-26; 80
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0009)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 2, 2006 March 24-26; 81
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0010)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 3, 2006 March 24-26; 82
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0011)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 3a, 2006 March 24-26; 83
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0012)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 4, 2006 March 24-26; 84
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0013)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 5, 2006 March 24-26; 85
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0014)
    - Local Studies, a National Movement Disk 6, 2006 March 24-26; 86
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0015)
    - Judy Richardson #1, 2006 June 4; 76
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0007)
    - Judy Richardson #2, 2006 June 4; 77
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0008)
    - Judy Richardson #3, 2006 June 4; 78
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0009)
    - Judy Richardson #4, 2006 June 4; 79
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0010)
    - Interview with Judy Richardson April 2007 #1, 2007 April; 87
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0004)
    - Interview with Judy Richardson April 2007 #2, 2007 April; 88
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0005)
    - The History Makers, 2007 April 9; 89
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0050)
    - A Veil of Secrecy: Orangeburg Massacre, Rough Cut (12.21.07), 2007 December 21; 91
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0042)
    - Slave Catchers, Slave Resisters, 2008; 90
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0028)
    - The Orangeburg Massacre, Fine Cut, 2008 May 16; 92
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0032)
    - The Orangeburg Massacre, 2008 May 16; 93
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0033)
    - Election Night Broadcast, 2008 November 4; 94
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0002)
    - The Jordan Rich Show: Interview with Judy Richardson, 2009 March; 96
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0002)
    - The Marc Steiner Show: Interview with Judy Richardson, 2009 April 9; 95
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0001)
    - The Kojo Nnamdi Show (WAMU): Women of SNCC [interview with Judy Richardson], 2010 October 5; 99
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0003)
    - Hands on the Freedom Plow, 2010; 97
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0007)
    - A Journey to Understanding, a film by O.M. Ajayi, 2010, 98
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0006)
    - Hands on the Freedom Plow (Martin Luther King Jr Commemoration), 2012 March 8; 101
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0008)
    - Unedited Interview Scholars Online, 2012 April 10; 100
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0001)
    - Judy Richardson Interview with Josh Davis Part 1, 2012 October 11; 102
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0019)
    - Judy Richardson Interview with Josh Davis Part 2, 2012 October 11; 103
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0020)
    - The Choices Program - Freedom Now: The Civil Rights Movement in Mississippi Disc 1, 2012; 104
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0048)
    - The Choices Program - Freedom Now: The Civil Rights Movement in Mississippi Disc 2, 2012; 105
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0049)
    - We'll Never Turn Back, Voices of the Civil Rights Movement, John F Kennedy Library Foundation Conference, Panel 1, 2013 March 07; 106
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0003)
    - We'll Never Turn Back, Voices of the Civil Rights Movement, John F Kennedy Library Foundation Conference, Panel 2, 2013 March 07; 107
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0004)
    - We'll Never Turn Back, Voices of the Civil Rights Movement, John F Kennedy Library Foundation Conference, Freedom Songs, 2013 March 07; 108
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0005)
    - "But I Only Told..." and "A Stranger is a Stranger is a Stranger", undated; 109
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0032)
    - "Memories of the Crisis", undated; 110
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0046)
    - "Memories of the Crisis", undated; 111
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0047)
    - "Night Talk" "Mississippi Burning" with Judy Richardson, Muriel Till... and Bob Law #1, undated; 112
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0003)
    - "Night Talk" "Mississippi Burning" with Judy Richardson, Muriel Till... and Bob Law #2, undated; 113
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0004)
    - "Power of the Media", undated; 114
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0039)
    - 1st Pink Light (Eloise Greenfield, author), Antioch (Biloti), undated; 115
      - Original 1/4" open reel audio tape (Box 20, Audio-reel RL10177-RR-0001)
    - A Foundation for Leadership in Discovery, undated; 116
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0036)
    - A Fragile Freedom: African American Historic Sites, undated; 117
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0041)
    - A Fragile Freedom: African American Historic Sites, undated; 118
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0037)
    - Africans in America promotional reel, undated; 119
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0033)
    - Cambridge Forum Radio, Judy Richardson as Moderator, Vincent Harding: Is America Possible? A Journey of Hope, undated; 120
      - Original audio compact disc (Box 17, Audio-disc RL10177-CD-0006)
    - Celebrating: A Foundation for Discovery, undated; 121
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0043)
    - Commission for Racial Justice "Purposes and Goals", undated; 122
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0011)
    - Expect Great Things: Shaping the Lived of Youth, undated; 123
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0020)
    - High Tide of Black Resistance, undated; 124
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0034)
    - In Our Lives: Civil Rights Parts 1 and 2, undated; 125
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0007)
    - Internet Safety Tips "open", undated; 126
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0008)
    - Interview with Judy Richardson in Champaign IL, undated; 127
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 20, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0059)
    - Living with Jim Crow, undated; 128
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0024)
    - Mississippi Burning Symposium and SNCC Reunion, undated; 129
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0006)
    - Niteline Show History: "Mississippi Burning", undated; 130
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0052)
    - No Matter How Small, undated; 131
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0016)
    - SNCC Freedom Singers "We Shall Overcome", undated; 132
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0002)
    - Streets of Greenwood-SNCC, undated; 133
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0002)
  - Voiceover and other materials, 1990-2012; 2
    - untitled, 1989 February 7; 1
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0016)
    - Judy on WGBH "Pledge" Nights, 1991 March 13; 2
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0015)
    - Latex Allergies, 1995 October 10; 3
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0027)
    - untitled, 1996 April 19; 4
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0012)
    - Latex Allergies, 1996 August 24; 5
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0032)
    - Latex Allergies, 1996 August 24; 6
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0034)
    - Latex, 1996 November; 7
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0037)
    - Latex Allergies, 1996 November 10; 8
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0028)
    - Jerry Anderson Part 2, 1996 November 7; 9
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0026)
    - Latex, Dr. Sullivan, 1996 November 7; 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0033)
    - Dr. Sullivan Part 2, 1996 November 7; 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0035)
    - Latex, circa 1996; 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0036)
    - Latex, circa 1996; 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0038)
    - Latex Allergy, circa 1996; 14
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0025)
    - Latex Tape, circa 1996; 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0024)
    - WGBH/AIA Promo Reel Narration Judy RIchardson, 1997 May 3; 16
      - Original Mini-DV videocassette (Box 17, Audio-cassette RL10177-MDV-0004)
    - Schizophrenia, 1999 September 9; 17
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0007)
    - Eyes, Dr. Seffel's Focus Group, undated; 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box 21, Audio-cassette RL10177-CS-0031)
    - Focus on the Brain: Clinical Practices for Special Care Nurseries, undated; 19
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0018)
    - Focus on the Brain: The Science of Preterm Infant Development, undated; 20
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0017)
    - Freedom Riders: The Children Shall Lead, undated; 21
      - Original DVD videodisc (Box 17, Video-disc RL10177-DVD-0052)
    - Hello Family: Because You're Pregnant, undated; 22
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0028)
    - Hello Family: News about Newborns, undated; 23
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0030)
    - News About Newborns, undated; 35
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0042)
    - Hello Family: Starting Out Safe and Sound, undated; 24
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0031)
    - Hello Family: Works of Wonder, undated; 25
      - Original VHS videocassette (Box 19, Video-cassette RL10177-VHS-0029)
    - Laser Surgery South Riding VA, undated; 26
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0001)
    - Laser Eyes, undated; 27
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0003)
    - Laser Eyes, undated; 28
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 18, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0004)
    - Laser Eyes, undated; 29
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0014)
    - Laser Eyes, undated; 30
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0015)
    - Laser Eyes, undated; 31
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0016)
    - Laser Surgery, undated; 32
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0009)
    - Laser Surgery, undated; 33
      - Original Betacam videocassette (Box 22, Video-cassette RL10177-Bcam-0011)